Guide to the Stanford Cohort Study Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-2000-184
  - Wordelman, Lisa Annette (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Workman, Stephan Gerard (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Wright, Christopher C. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Wright, Constance S. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Wright, Jeffrey Wayne (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Wuthnow, Julie (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Yokoe, Deborah S. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Zaro, David Robert (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Zarucchi, Carol May (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Zimmerman, Lyle B. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Austin, Dorothy A. H. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Bedont, Cynthia A. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Block, Evan D. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Braslow, Rebekah A. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Corman, Craig A. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Coulter, David B. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Curry, James E. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Dvorak, Richard D. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - El-hibri, Fuad Y. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Ensley, Ralph D. (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Farman, Charles S. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Forbes, Naushad (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Frost, Catherine S. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Gould, Laurie J. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Groswold, Karol A. (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Hefner, Mark D. (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Higuera, Maria E. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Hooton, Michael R. (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Huang, Virgina S. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Kerst, Dianna S. (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Kong, Vivan W. (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Kulhanian, Julie A. (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Lindgren, Jonathan S. (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Lee, Patricia L. (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Lyon, David E. (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Mays, Lora D. (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - McGowan, Mark J. (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Meier, David K. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Mitchell, Alan B. (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Mitchell, Teri E. (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Miyawaki, Natolie C. (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Murphy, Mark T. (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - O'Leary, Timothy F. (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Paladini, Daniel G. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Pierret, Charles R. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Poplawski, Edward (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Prati, Massimo (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Pratt, Lizbeth L. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Quinn, Bruce C. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Rosner, Elizabeth J. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Sills, Gregory D. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Skardal, Ellen T. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Smiley, Brian R. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Snorf, Cynthia R. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Vujovich, Bron (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Wilson, Curtis S. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Wilson, Debra S. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Woolner, Stanley A. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Yamanaka, Dawn M. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Young, Bret L. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Adams, Carol Lynn (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Andersen, William Robert (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Barger, Mary Catherine (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Barnecut, Leland Jennings (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Bennet-Penna, Jonelle Ruth (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Boadwee, Harry (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Bowen, Carol Lynn (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Bugas, John Andrew (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Bunker, Emily L. (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Campbell, Thomas Douglas (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Chinn, Susan Elizabeth (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Clark, Christopher Hawes (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Cohn, Allen Steven (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Dovey, Michael Garde (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Ferguson, Paul Francis (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Gass, Linda Irene (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Gehn, Lisa Marie (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Gibson, Susan Irma (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Goedhart, Janis Nicole (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Gore, Faith Louise (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Guthrie, Carol Ruth (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Hastings, Leslie Anne (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Hilsinger, Jeanne Louise (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Hrabik, Donna Marie (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Itin, Mary Elizabeth (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Johnson, Jeannene (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Kotler, Ellen Maxine (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Lammers, James Donald (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Matsumoto, Maria Aya (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Mayers, Michael Curtis (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Miles, Susan Ann (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Morissey, Melissa Ann (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Mouchawar, Maurice Aref (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Nelson, Gregory Mark (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Nieves, Ruben A. (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Noss, Martha Jane (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Ott, Gregory Alan (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Pond, Elizabeth Burchal (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Prince, Erica Dianne (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Roe, Brian Michael (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Ross, Richard Jonathan (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Rubin, Bruce Jay (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Scharff, Eric Ian (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Scoles, Nancy Ann (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Sherman, David Soltz (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Stauffer, Deborah (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Stupfel, Mark Joseph (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Tout, Anne E. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Villesvik, Sanford Malcolm (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Worden, William Thomas (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Transfer Students' Alumni Assessments (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Senior Surveys (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Cohort Study Follw-Up Misc. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Senior Surveys (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Originals-Forms, Letters, etc.-Cohort Study (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Cohort Follow-Up-Extra Copies of Roster (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Cohort Follow-up-Roster (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Name and address card file and cards for "follow-up of interview sample" (Box 16)
- Computer files, Accession ARCH-2001-057; 2 computer media (Box 1)
  AU 1261 Curriculum Study Files and AU 1256 Best Cohort Files
- Audio recordings, Accession ARCH-2002-225
  - Report: Steven #203, 0 (Box 1)
  - Report: Kathryn #249, 0 (Box 1)
  - Report: John #111, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Barbara #211, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: John #56, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Dawn #56, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: John #82, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Jeff #253, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Drue #35, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Ron #165, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Vicharia #84, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Rebecca #251, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Susan #69, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Kevin #189, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Rose #62, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Judy #233, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Janice #248 and Jeff #153, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Keith #25, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Emily #301, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Mimi #255, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Ami #188, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Alan #307, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: John #154, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: John #234, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Vichar #197, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Russel # 162, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: John #296, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Larry #80, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Jennifer #291, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Charles #30, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Curt #159, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Ted #204, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Peter #53, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Paul #125, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Nora #117, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Report: Mike #216, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 1)
  - Interview: Jrue #35, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: John #154, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Ken #150, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jeff #153, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Kris #171, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jene #131, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Rose #62, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jo #47, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Nora #117, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Pat #243, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jeff #253, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: James #46, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Kevin #189, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Ann #188, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Bill #139, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: #59, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Ina #51, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jae #132, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Charles #30, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Dibarab, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Richard #58, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Steven #203, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Ted #204, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Ron #165, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Alan #307, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jean #138, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Keith #25, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: 294722 #296, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jaun #56, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Cohort #004, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Cohort Shari #201, 33354; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Mark #294, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Rebecca #251, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Jaime #248, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Monte #431, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Darrin #212, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Victor #197, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Mike #216, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 2)
  - Interview: Valencia #181, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Rusell #162, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Curt #159, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Teal #68, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: #134, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Lorr #278, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Anna #143, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Patti #285, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: #100, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Larry #801, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: John #111, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Tyrone #236, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Marie #113, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Garid #2261, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: #254, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Sinalhovn #295, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Paul #501, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: #225, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: #225 Part 2, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Paul #48, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Eushy #301, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: 2943944 #235, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Glenn #271, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Peter #53, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Susan #93, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Vretana #84, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Linda #14, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Jaclyn #142, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Kathryn #249, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: #211, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Kim #67, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Casey #255, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Jody #233, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: John #234, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: Robert #24, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Interview: John #82, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 3)
  - Jill Shoemaker #263, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Cohort: Ken #228 ID #2952892, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Cohort: Teresa #089 ID #2943444, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Ruth #038 [Two Sides], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - #2955955 #221, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Gayle #190 [Two Sides], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Judy #012, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Leon #10, 33440; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Barbara #182, 33456; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - John Celond #164, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Cohort: Robert (Scott) #079 ID #2947280, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - #2951455 #166, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - #220, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Leslie #206 [Two Sides], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Cohort: Heidi #115 ID #2940292, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - 2943886 #5 Euler, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Interview: Alex #274, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Bob #24, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Glenn #271, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: David #100, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Paul #48, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Susan #134, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Kim #67, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Peter #59, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Pat #243, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Jennifer #291 (cont.), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Report: Monty #43, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Todd Timberlake #284, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Kathryn Doi #63 (beginning), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Kathryn Doi #63 (2nd Tape), 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Tom Friedberg #85, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Margeret Feher #195 [Two Sides], 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Richard #027, 33415; 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Interview: Bill Bunting #44, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)
  - Jennifer Euver #2946425, 1 audiocassette(s) (Box 4)